[
  {
    "id": "843",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What does Amazon SWF stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "Simple Wireless Forms",
        "Simple Web Form",
        "Simple Work Flow",
        "Simple Web Flow"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Simple Work Flow"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "844",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What does Amazon SES stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "Software Enabled Server",
        "Simple Email Service",
        "Simple Elastic Server",
        "Software Email Solution"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Simple Email Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "845",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What happens when you create a topic on Amazon SNS?",
      "answers": [
        "The topic will terminate your EC2 instances without a tag.",
        "You can create a topic on Amazon SQS not on SNS.",
        "You cannot create a topic on SNS.",
        "An Amazon Resource Name is created"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["An Amazon Resource Name is created"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "846",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is the difference between SNS and SQS?",
      "answers": [
        "SQS sends messages to people on topics, where as SNS manages tasks",
        "SNS pulls (polls) where as SQS is push based message service",
        "SQS and SNS are basically the same service",
        "SNS is push notification service, where as SQS is message system that requires worker nodes to poll the queue."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SNS is push notification service, where as SQS is message system that requires worker nodes to poll the queue."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "847",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What application service allows you to decouple your infrastructure using messaged based queues?",
      "answers": [
        "SNS",
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "848",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What does a 'domain' refer to in Amazon SWF?",
      "answers": [
        "A security group in which only tasks inside can initiate",
        "A special type of worker",
        "The DNS record for the Amazon SWF service",
        "A collection of related workflows"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["A collection of related workflows"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "849",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "By default, EC2 instances pull SQS messages from an SQS queue on a FIFO (First In First out) basis.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "850",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon's SQS service guarantees a message will be delivered at least once.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "851",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon SWF ensures that a task is assigned only once and is never duplicated.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "852",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Amazon SWF restrict me to use specific programming languages.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "853",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS is a ________ based system component",
      "answers": [
        "pull",
        "push"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["pull"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "854",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SNS is a ________ based system component",
      "answers": [
        "pull",
        "push"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["push"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "855",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which AWS service allows you to decouple the components of your application?",
      "answers": [
        "SQS",
        "SNS",
        "SES",
        "SMS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "856",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of distributed application components can store a message in an SQS queue?",
      "answers": [
        "any component",
        "none",
        "node.js components",
        "custom components"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["any component"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "857",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS messages can contain up to _____ of text in ________ format?",
      "answers": [
        "256KB, any",
        "256KB, XML",
        "256KB, JSON",
        "128KB, any"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["256KB, any"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "858",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Any distributed application component can retrieve messages programatically from the queue using _________?",
      "answers": [
        "the SQS API",
        "the AWS console",
        "the SNS API",
        "the S3 API"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the SQS API"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "859",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "How does SQS help in your distributed system design?",
      "answers": [
        "it allows for the situation when the message producing component is producing work faster than the message consuming component can process the messages",
        "when your message producing component and/or your message consuming component are intermittently available (when you're using spot instances, for example)",
        "it allows you to push messages to many receiving components through topics",
        "it allows you to create workflows with directors and workers",
        "you can use auto-scaling groups to monitor messages in your queue, and scale up or down your processing app EC2 instances if the queue gets too full or drains down to very low"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["it allows for the situation when the message producing component is producing work faster than the message consuming component can process the messages",
        "when your message producing component and/or your message consuming component are intermittently available (when you're using spot instances, for example)",
        "you can use auto-scaling groups to monitor messages in your queue, and scale up or down your processing app EC2 instances if the queue gets too full or drains down to very low"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "860",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the two types of SQS queues?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Queues",
        "FIFO Queues",
        "Simple Queues",
        "Distributed Queues",
        "Restricted Queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Standard Queues",
        "FIFO Queues"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "861",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which SQS queue type is the default type?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Queues",
        "FIFO Queues",
        "Simple Queues",
        "Distributed Queues",
        "Restricted Queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Standard Queues"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "862",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "How many transactions per second can the SQS standard queue handle?",
      "answers": [
        "nearly unlimited",
        "1,000",
        "100,000",
        "1,000,000",
        "100"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["nearly unlimited"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "863",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS standard queues guarantee that _________?",
      "answers": [
        "a message is delivered at least once",
        "a message is delivered",
        "a message is processed",
        "a message is deleted"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a message is delivered at least once"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "864",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS standard queues offer _________?",
      "answers": [
        "best-effort ordering",
        "exact ordering",
        "random ordering",
        "descending sequence ordering"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["best-effort ordering"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "865",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS standard queue best-effort ordering ensures __________?",
      "answers": [
        "that messages are generally delivered in the same order they are sent",
        "that messages are in the same order they are sent",
        "that messages are in the random order",
        "that messages are not dropped"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["that messages are generally delivered in the same order they are sent"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "866",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS FIFO queues offer __________?",
      "answers": [
        "first-in-first-out delivery and exactly once processing",
        "first-in-first-out delivery and usually once processing",
        "first-in-first-out delivery with duplicate processing",
        "first-out-first-in delivery and exactly once processing"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["first-in-first-out delivery and exactly once processing"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "867",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS FIFO queues, the order in which ____________ is strictly preserved?",
      "answers": [
        "the messages are sent and received",
        "the messages are sent",
        "the messages are received",
        "the messages are processed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the messages are sent and received"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "868",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS FIFO queues, the message is delivered ________?",
      "answers": [
        "once",
        "occasionally multiple times"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["once"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "869",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS FIFO queues, the message remains available until ________?",
      "answers": [
        "a consumer processes and deletes it",
        "a consumer processes it",
        "its TTL (Time To Live) expires"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a consumer processes and deletes it"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "870",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS FIFO queues ________?",
      "answers": [
        "duplicates are not introduced into the queue",
        "duplicates are allows into the queue",
        "multiples are allowed into the queue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["duplicates are not introduced into the queue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "871",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which SQS queue type offers message groups?",
      "answers": [
        "Standard Queues",
        "FIFO Queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["FIFO Queues"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "872",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS message groups allow ________?",
      "answers": [
        "multiple ordered message groups within a single queue",
        "multiple ordered message groups within multiple queues",
        "a single ordered message group within a single queue",
        "a single ordered message group within multiple queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple ordered message groups within a single queue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "873",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS FIFO queues are limited to how many transactions per second?",
      "answers": [
        "nearly unlimited",
        "1,000",
        "100,000",
        "1,000,000",
        "300"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["300"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "874",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS, messages can be kept in the queue for how long?",
      "answers": [
        "from 1 minute to 14 days",
        "from 1 day to 14 days",
        "from 1 hour to 14 days",
        "from 1 minute to 7 days",
        "from 1 minute to 1 day"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["from 1 minute to 14 days"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "875",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS, the default time a message can be kept in the queue is _________?",
      "answers": [
        "4 days",
        "1 day",
        "30 minutes",
        "1 hour",
        "7 days"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["4 days"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "876",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS, the visibility timeout is _______?",
      "answers": [
        "the amount of time that the message is invisible in the SQS queue after a consumer picks up that message",
        "the amount of time that the message is visible in the queue",
        "the amount of time before the message is visible",
        "the amount of time the message is visible"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the amount of time that the message is invisible in the SQS queue after a consumer picks up that message"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "877",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With the SQS visibility timeout, provided that the job is processed before the visibility timeout expires, the message will then be ________?",
      "answers": [
        "deleted from the queue",
        "moved to the dead letter queue",
        "moved to the fron of the queue",
        "moved to the end of the queue",
        "visible again"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["deleted from the queue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "878",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With the SQS visibility timeout, if the job is not processed before the visibility timeout expires, the message will then ________?",
      "answers": [
        "deleted from the queue",
        "moved to the dead letter queue",
        "moved to the fron of the queue",
        "moved to the end of the queue",
        "become visible again"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["become visible again"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "879",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With the SQS visibility timeout, if the job is not processed before the visibility timeout expires, the message will then become visible again. This could result in ________?",
      "answers": [
        "the same message being delivered twice",
        "the message being moved to the dead letter queue",
        "the message beingmoved to the fron of the queue",
        "the message beingmoved to the end of the queue"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the same message being delivered twice"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "880",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The SQS visibility timeout maximum is ______",
      "answers": [
        "12 hours",
        "1 day",
        "1 hour",
        "60 seconds"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["12 hours"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "881",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SQS guarantees that _________",
      "answers": [
        "your messages will be delivered at least once",
        "your messages will be delivered",
        "your messages will be consumed",
        "your messages will be queued"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["your messages will be delivered at least once"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "882",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "What are the two types of SQS polling?",
      "answers": [
        "long polling",
        "short polling",
        "fast polling",
        "delayed polling",
        "synchronous polling"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["long polling",
        "short polling"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "883",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "With SQS long polling, your polling call doesn't return until ________?",
      "answers": [
        "a message arrives in the queue",
        "the long poll call times out",
        "the queue closes",
        "the long poll call is interrupted",
        "the polling function terminates"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a message arrives in the queue",
        "the long poll call times out"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "884",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SQS short polling, your polling call _________?",
      "answers": [
        "returns immediately, even if the queue being polled is empty",
        "returns after a set timeout, even if the queue being polled is empty",
        "returns immediately, and gives a warning if the queue is empty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["returns immediately, even if the queue being polled is empty"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "885",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF is __________?",
      "answers": [
        "a web service that coordinates work across distributed application components and even manual tasks",
        "a web service that coordinates work across distributed application components but not manual tasks",
        "a web service that queues work across distributed application components"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a web service that coordinates work across distributed application components and even manual tasks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "886",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "What are some of the use cases for SWF?",
      "answers": [
        "media processing",
        "web application back-ends",
        "business process workflows",
        "analytics pipelines",
        "financial transactions",
        "social networks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["media processing",
        "web application back-ends",
        "business process workflows",
        "analytics pipelines"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "887",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF use cases are designed as _________?",
      "answers": [
        "a coordination of tasks",
        "a set of sequential steps",
        "a set of random steps",
        "highly parallel sets of tasks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a coordination of tasks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "887",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 4",
      "question": "SWF tasks represent invocations of various processing steps in an application which can be performed by _________?",
      "answers": [
        "executable code",
        "web service calls",
        "human actions",
        "scripts",
        "message queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["executable code",
        "web service calls",
        "human actions",
        "scripts"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "888",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF workers are ________?",
      "answers": [
        "programs that interact with SWF",
        "programs that run SWF tasks",
        "humans that interact with SWF"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["programs that interact with SWF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "889",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "SWF workers do which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "get tasks",
        "process received tasks",
        "return the results of a processed task",
        "start the SWF process"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["get tasks",
        "process received tasks",
        "return the results of a processed task"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "890",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF deciders are ________?",
      "answers": [
        "a program that controls the coordination of tasks",
        "a program that schedules the tasks",
        "a human worker that controls the coordination of tasks",
        "a human worker that schedules the tasks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["a program that controls the coordination of tasks"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "891",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "In SWF which of these is an application that can initiate a workflow?",
      "answers": [
        "decider",
        "worker",
        "workflow starter",
        "workflow decider"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["workflow starter"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "892",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "In SWF, which of these are examples of workflow starters?",
      "answers": [
        "web application",
        "mobile app",
        "human",
        "natural event"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["web application",
        "mobile app"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "893",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "In SWF, workers and the decider can run on cloud infrastrucute such as _________?",
      "answers": [
        "EC2 instances",
        "machines behind firewalls",
        "CloudFront",
        "Snowball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instances",
        "machines behind firewalls"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "894",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF _______ between workers and the decider?",
      "answers": [
        "brokers the interactions",
        "distributes workload",
        "schedules tasks"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["brokers the interactions"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "895",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF ensures that a task is ___________?",
      "answers": [
        "assigned only once and is never duplicated",
        "assigned and sometimes can be duplicated",
        "assigned",
        "executed"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["assigned only once and is never duplicated"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "896",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is the key difference between SQS and SWF?",
      "answers": [
        "SQS can have duplicated tasks but SWF will never duplicate a task",
        "SWF can have duplicated tasks but SQS will never duplicate a task",
        "SWF is queue based and SQS is workflow based",
        "SWF is fault tolerant but SQS is not"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS can have duplicated tasks but SWF will never duplicate a task"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "897",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF can scale quickly because _________?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF maintains the application's state durably, so workers and deciders don't have to keep track of execution state",
        "SWF is a managed service",
        "SWF is distributed across all of your AZs",
        "SWF is fault tolerant"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SWF maintains the application's state durably, so workers and deciders don't have to keep track of execution state"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "898",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF workflows, activity types, and the workflow execution itself are scoped to a _______?",
      "answers": [
        "domain",
        "region",
        "set of AZs",
        "fleet of EC2 instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["domain"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "899",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF workflow domains isolate a set of types, executions, and task lists from  others within the same _______?",
      "answers": [
        "account",
        "region",
        "set of AZs",
        "organization"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["account"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "900",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "You can register an SWF domain by ________?",
      "answers": [
        "using the AWS console",
        "using the RegisterDomain action in the SWF API",
        "using the RegisterAction SWF API",
        "using the cli"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["using the AWS console",
        "using the RegisterDomain action in the SWF API"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "901",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF domain parameters are specified in _______ format?",
      "answers": [
        "JSON",
        "XML",
        "plain text",
        "AJAX"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["JSON"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "902",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "The maximum an SWF workflow can run is _________?",
      "answers": [
        "1 year",
        "1 hour",
        "1 month",
        "1 day"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["1 year"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "903",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SWF workflows are measured in _________?",
      "answers": [
        "seconds",
        "milliseconds",
        "minutes",
        "hours"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["seconds"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "904",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these offers a task-oriented API?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SWF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "905",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these offers a message-oriented API?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "906",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With which of these do you not need to keep track of all tasks and events in an application because the service does it for you?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SWF"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "907",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With which of these do you need to implement your own application-level tracking especially if your application uses multiple queues?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "908",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With which of these is a web service that allows you to set up, operate, and send notifications from the cloud?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SNS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "909",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of these provides developers with a highly scalable, flexible, and cost effective capability to push messages from an application and immediately deliver them to subscribers or other applications?",
      "answers": [
        "SWF",
        "SQS",
        "SES",
        "SNS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SNS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "910",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Besides pushing notifications directly to mobile devices, SNS can also deliver notifications via SMS text message or email to which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "SQS queues",
        "any HTTP endpoint",
        "CloudWatch",
        "CloudFront"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS queues",
        "any HTTP endpoint"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "911",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SNS notifications can trigger lambda functions?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "912",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When a message is published to an SNS topic that has a lambda function subscribed to it, the lambda function in invoked with the payload of _______?",
      "answers": [
        "the published message",
        "the message topic",
        "the message meta-data",
        "the message pointer"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["the published message"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "913",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "SNS allows you to group multiple recipients using ______?",
      "answers": [
        "topics",
        "domains",
        "meta-data",
        "subjects"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["topics"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "914",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SNS, one topic can support deliveries to __________?",
      "answers": [
        "multiple end-point types",
        "one end-point type",
        "defined end-point types",
        "SQS queues"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple end-point types"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "915",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "To prevent messages from being loast, all messages published to SNS are stored redundantly across ________?",
      "answers": [
        "multiple AZs",
        "multiple regions",
        "multiple EFS mount-points",
        "multiple EC2 instances"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["multiple AZs"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "915",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With SNS you have no up-front costs and a pay-as-you-go pricing model?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "916",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which service is a media transcoder in the cloud",
      "answers": [
        "Elastic Transcoder",
        "ElasticSearch",
        "Elastic Translator",
        "Media Transcoder"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Elastic Transcoder"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "917",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which service is a fully managed service that makes it easy for developers to publish, maintain, monitor, and secure APIs at any scale",
      "answers": [
        "API Gateway",
        "Lambda",
        "API Manager",
        "SQS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["API Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "918",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "You can enable _____ in API Gateway to cache your endpoint's response",
      "answers": [
        "API caching",
        "Lambda caching",
        "API management",
        "API redundancy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["API caching"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "919",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you enable API caching, API Gateway caches responses from your end-point for a specified _______ period in _______",
      "answers": [
        "TTL, seconds",
        "TTL, in milliseconds",
        "TTD, in seconds",
        "TTD, in milliseconds"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["TTL, seconds"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "920",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "With API Gateway you can _______",
      "answers": [
        "scale your end-points effortlessly",
        "throttle requests to prevent DDoS attacks",
        "connect to CloudWatch to log all requests",
        "have human tasks as steps in your process"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["scale your end-points effortlessly",
        "throttle requests to prevent DDoS attacks",
        "connect to CloudWatch to log all requests"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "921",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Under this policy, a web browser permits scripts contained in a first web page to access data in a second web page, but only if they both have the same origin, meaning they have the same domain name",
      "answers": [
        "same origin policy",
        "multiple origin policy",
        "domain name policy",
        "AWS domain policy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["same origin policy"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "922",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ is a way the server at the other end can relax the same origin policy",
      "answers": [
        "CORS, cross-origin resource sharing",
        "ORS, origin resource sharing",
        "DORS, domain-origin resource sharing",
        "AWS domain policy"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["CORS, cross-origin resource sharing"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "923",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When you see 'Error - 'Origin policy cannont be read at the remote resource', you need to _________",
      "answers": [
        "enable CORS on API Gateway",
        "disable CORS on API Gateway",
        "Recreate your API Gateway",
        "Switch to something other than API Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["enable CORS on API Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "924",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What is the AWS service to which you can send your streaming data?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis",
        "EC2",
        "SQS",
        "SWF"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "925",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "What are the three Kinesis services?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "Kinesis Firehose",
        "Kinesis Analytics",
        "Kinesis Warehouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Streams",
        "Kinesis Firehose",
        "Kinesis Analytics"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "926",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the three Kinesis services stores data in shards?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "Kinesis Firehose",
        "Kinesis Analytics",
        "Kinesis Warehouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Streams"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "927",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the three Kinesis services allows you to analyze the data sent through it using lambda functions in real-time?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "Kinesis Firehose",
        "Kinesis Analytics",
        "Kinesis Warehouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Firehose"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "928",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which of the three Kinesis services allows you to analyze the data sent through it using lambda functions in real-time and then send the analyzed data to S3 or ElasticSearch clusters. After the data goes to S3 or ElasticSearch it can then be copied to Redshift?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "Kinesis Firehose",
        "Kinesis Analytics",
        "Kinesis Warehouse"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Kinesis Firehose"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "929",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "If your job runs for greater than 12 hours, which service should you not use because its visibility timeout maximum is 12 hours?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "SQS",
        "SNS",
        "SWF"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "930",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Application Services",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 5",
      "question": "Which of these are SNS subscriber types?",
      "answers": [
        "Kinesis Streams",
        "SQS",
        "HTTP/S",
        "email",
        "email-JSON",
        "lambda",
        "CloudWatch"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SQS",
        "HTTP/S",
        "email",
        "email-JSON",
        "lambda"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "931",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When using CloudFront, how can you guard your content from being served without your application serving it up?",
      "answers": [
        "use url rewrite rules",
        "use restricted urls via ip blocking in Security Groups",
        "use restricted urls via ip blocking in your NACLs",
        "use GuardDuty"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["use url rewrite rules"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "932",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When using Auto-Scaling Groups, you must first create a _________ to describe the instances to launch?",
      "answers": [
        "launch configuration",
        "target group",
        "placement group",
        "elastic ip"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["launch configuration"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "933",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "VPC",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "When using Auto-Scaling Groups, you _______ to launch your instances?",
      "answers": [
        "use AMIs",
        "use target groups",
        "use placement groups",
        "use elastic ips"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["use AMIs"]
    }
  }
]
